[
    {
        "ques_no": "1",
        "question": "What is Flutter?",
        "a": "A programming language",
        "b": "A database system",
        "c": "A UI toolkit by Google",
        "d": "An operating system",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "2",
        "question": "Which language is used to write Flutter apps?",
        "a": "Java",
        "b": "Dart",
        "c": "Kotlin",
        "d": "Swift",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "3",
        "question": "Which company developed Flutter?",
        "a": "Apple",
        "b": "Facebook",
        "c": "Google",
        "d": "Microsoft",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "4",
        "question": "Flutter is mainly used for developing:",
        "a": "Websites only",
        "b": "Android apps only",
        "c": "Desktop apps only",
        "d": "Cross-platform mobile apps",
        "correct": "d",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "5",
        "question": "What is a widget in Flutter?",
        "a": "A type of database",
        "b": "A small app",
        "c": "A building block of UI",
        "d": "A programming function",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "6",
        "question": "Which method runs first in a Flutter app?",
        "a": "build()",
        "b": "main()",
        "c": "runApp()",
        "d": "start()",
        "correct": "b",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "7",
        "question": "Which widget is used to create scrollable content?",
        "a": "Text",
        "b": "Column",
        "c": "ListView",
        "d": "Container",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "8",
        "question": "What does 'hot reload' mean in Flutter?",
        "a": "Restarts the system",
        "b": "Clears the memory",
        "c": "Updates UI without restarting app",
        "d": "Uninstalls the app",
        "correct": "c",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "9",
        "question": "Which of the following is a state management method?",
        "a": "Provider",
        "b": "StatelessWidget",
        "c": "build()",
        "d": "runApp()",
        "correct": "a",
        "answer": "e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "10",
        "question": "Which file is the entry point of a Flutter project?",
        "a": "main.html",
        "b": "home.dart",
        "c": "app.dart",
        "d": "main.dart",
        "correct": "d",
        "answer": "e"
    }
]
